

Jimi Jenneskens

BSc Logistic Engineer | Data Analyst

Privada Boca Negra 600 2, Monterrey, 64800, Mexico +5219843231663 · jimijenneskens@gmail.com

⇔ <u>LinkedIn</u>, <u>GitHub</u>

Date / Place of birth

31-01-1994, Venray, The Netherlands

Nationality

Dutch

Skills

Lean Management

ERP, WMS & TMS

IBM SPSS Statistics

SAP

Python

MySQL

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Languages

Dutch
English
Spanish
German

Profile

Passionate, initiative, analytical, flexible and results-oriented logistic engineer with two years of experience in supply chain logistics, warehousing & distribution and production logistics, who is currently specializing as a Data Analyst at the Tecnológico de Monterrey.

Employment History

Junior Business Support Engineer, Broekman Logistics, Venlo, The Netherlands

September 2018 - September 2019

- Analyzed and optimized the efficiency of logistic processes, such as transport planning and warehouse processes.
- Processed operational inbound- and outbound orders.
- Planned and prepared documents for transport to worldwide customers.
- Contributed to process optimization projects and to setting up the brand new warehouse in Venlo.

Bachelor Thesis & Interim Logistics Engineer, Wicro Plastics, Kessel, The Netherlands

January 2018 — August 2018

 Redesigned the flow of goods and information from warehouse to assembly lines, which resulted in a time saving of 22,49% in transportation time.

Customer Service Operator, ECS European Containers, Venlo, The Netherlands

July 2015 — November 2016

• Processed worldwide transport orders and offered customer support.

Education

Diplomado, Data Analyst, Tecnológico de Monterrey, Monterrey, Mexico July 2020 — January 2021

Acquiring competences in Advanced Excel, Fundamental Statistics, Python Programming, Databases, Front-End Web Visualization, JavaScript and Business Intelligence Software.

Bachelor of Science, Logistics Engineering, Fontys University of Applied Sciences, Venlo, The Netherlands

September 2014 — July 2018

Project based learning with topics as production logistics, transport logistics and supply chain management.

Minor, E-commerce & E-fulfillment, Fontys University of Applied Sciences, Venlo, The Netherlands

September 2016 — January 2017

Acquired entrepreneurial competences about E-commerce and

E-fulfillment to make an E-business successful.